<?xml version='1.0' standalone='yes'?>
<webapps>
	<item>
		<question>I am using Internet Explorer 6 (or earlier, &lt; 7.0), why does your site look like crap?</question>
		<faqanswer>Let's face it, Internet Explorer 6 is probably one of, if not the crappiest of browsers available. The Trident render engine included in IE 6 and earlier is not even up to par with web standards, and so it makes PNG images look bad, with a light blue background (unless I hack it, which I won't do), and it doesn't agree with all of the CSS 2 -- it doesn't support Web Standards! If you are using IE 6 on Windows XP, then please upgrade to IE 7, because Microsoft &lt;a href="http://www.microsoft.com/windows/support/endofsupport.mspx"&gt;stopped supporting that on 10 October 2006&lt;/a&gt;, but if you're using it on Windows 2000, then it's supposed to be supported until 2010 (sadly you can't upgrade to IE 7 on Windows 2000, however). If you cannot upgrade your browser, then use a third party browser that supports web standards, such as &lt;a href="http://www.mozilla.com/"&gt;Firefox&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.apple.com/safari/"&gt;Safari&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href="http://www.google.com/chrome"&gt;Chrome&lt;/a&gt;. If you are using a Macintosh and using IE 5 or earlier, then definitely upgrade, because Microsoft doesn't support that at all anymore, and why should they?</faqanswer>
	</item>
	<item>
		<question>What technologies did you use to create this website?</question>
		<faqanswer>I focus most of my work on &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Xhtml"&gt;XHTML&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Xml"&gt;XML&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cascading_Style_Sheets"&gt;CSS&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ecmascript"&gt;JavaScript&lt;/a&gt;. These are all web standards (see &lt;a href="http://www.w3.org/"&gt;W3C&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.webstandards.org/"&gt;The Web Standards Project&lt;/a&gt;. For my back end I typically utilize &lt;a href="http://www.php.net/"&gt;PHP&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://www.php.net/"&gt;ASP.NET&lt;/a&gt;. This website was written in PHP. My goal is to write as much as possible in pure client-side languages, but when security and validation play a role, I utilize back-end technologies such as PHP and ASP.NET. I also am able to produce websites using &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Common_Gateway_Interface"&gt;CGI&lt;/a&gt; scripts written in Perl and other scripting languages, though I did not do that here.</faqanswer>
	</item>
</webapps>